const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'Which sibling famously declared “Marcia, Marcia, Marcia”?',
    answers: [ 
      'Jan',
      'Cindy',
      'Greg',
      'Bobby',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Jan' ,
  },
  {
    question: 'In the "Not So Ugly Duckling", Jan makes up a name for her fake boyfriend. What is it?',
    answers: [
      'Josh Scotch',
      'George Glass',
      'Jeff Jett',
      'Simon Brown',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'George Glass',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the middle school the Brady kids attend?',
    answers: [
      'Fillmore Junior High',
      'Buchanan Junior High',
      'Hamlin Junior High',
      'Westdale Junior High',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Fillmore Junior High',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Alice’s last name?',
  answers: [
      'Brady',
      'Nelson',
      'Messerschidt',
      'Poppins',
  ],
  correctAnswer: 'Nelson',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which Brady kid is in the upper left corner of the opening credits?',
  answers: [
      'Cindy',
      'Marcia',
      'Greg',
      'Bobby',
  ],
  correctAnswer: 'Marcia',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of Cindy’s beloved doll?',
  answers: [
     'Chatty Kathy',
      'Talky Tina',
      'Miss Maisy',
      'Kitty Karry-All',
  ],
  correctAnswer: 'Kitty Karry-All',
  },
  {
    question: 'Who breaks Carols vase in “Confessions, confessions"?',
  answers: [
      'Greg',
      'Cindy',
      'Peter',
      'Bobby',
  ],
  correctAnswer: 'Peter',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the young cousin who comes to live with the Brady’s in the final season?',
  answers: [
      'Oliver',
      'Pip',
      'David',
      'Sam',
  ],
  correctAnswer: 'Oliver',
  },
  {
    question: 'The kitchen in the Brady house was decorated in what two colors?',
    answers: [
      'Black and white',
      'Red and blue',
      'Green and orange',
      'Red and white',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Green and orange',
  },
  {
    question: 'What did Mike Brady do for a living?',
    answers: [
      'Accountant',
      'Psychiatrist',
      'Architect',
      'Investor' ,
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Architect',
  },
  
  ]